All right, we like to say welcome
brothers and sisters to another
Wednesday question and answer where we
open up with the 10 Commandments that
God commanded the whole world to keep.
Brother Tanzil.
And God spake all these words saying,
I am the Lord thy God, which had brought
thee out of the land of Egypt,
out of the house of bondage. Thou shalt
have no other gods before me.
Thou shalt not make unto thee any graven
image, or any likeness of anything
that is in heaven above, or that is in
the earth beneath, [clears throat]
or that is in the water under the earth.
Thou shalt not bow down to
for I the Lord thy God am a jealous God,
visiting the iniquity of the fathers
upon the children unto the third and
fourth generation of them that hate me,
and showing mercy unto thousands of them
that love me, and keep my commandments.
Thou shalt not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain.
For the Lord will not hold him guiltless
that taketh his name in vain.
Remember the sabbath day, to keep it
holy.
Six days shalt thou labor and do all thy
work, but the seventh day
is the sabbath of the Lord thy God.
In it thou shalt not do any work, thou,
nor thy son, nor thy daughter, nor thy
manservant, nor thy maidservant, nor thy
cattle, nor that stranger that is within
thy gates. For in six days the Lord made
heaven and earth,
the sea, and all that in them is, and
rested the seventh day. Wherefore the
Lord blessed the sabbath day, and
hallowed it.
Honor thy father and thy mother, that
thy days may be long upon the land which
the Lord thy God giveth thee.
Thou shalt not kill. Thou shalt not
commit adultery.
Thou shalt not steal.
Thou shalt not bear false witness
against thy neighbor. Thou shalt not
covet thy neighbor's house, thou shalt
not covet thy neighbor's wife, nor his
manservant, nor his maidservant, nor his
ox, nor his ass, nor anything that is
thy neighbor's.
We read Exodus 20:1-17.
May the Lord have a blessing to the
reading of his words. In Jesus' name we
pray.
Amen.
So here on question and answer, you can
ask us a question and we'll answer it
according to the King James Bible. And
if we cannot find the answer, we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time. The questions we
will not answer are the vague, as well
as the long scripture questions, and
questions of debate. We are not here to
debate, we are here to spread the true
gospel of Jesus. So please be as direct
as possible with your questions so we
can be as direct as possible with our
answers out of the King James Bible. No
other Bibles or books will be
acknowledged on this program. Also keep
in mind this is a live this is a live
stream, so feel free to send in your
questions that pertain to everlasting
life. We just ask that you please keep
them to a two scripture maximum.
Let me introduce to you the family
that's on the panel this evening. We got
brother Dre.
Good evening.
Brother Julius. Good evening, everybody.
Brother Jerome.
Grace and peace.
Brother Tanzil.
Good evening, everyone.
Sister Deborah.
Good evening.
Brother Sean.
And we have the guest caller with us and
I'm brother Cornell.
And sister Deborah, before we get
started this evening, I just wanted to
let all of our viewing audience from all
around the world know
that next Wednesday, April 1st, there
will not be a question and answer. Next
Wednesday, April 1st, there will not be
a question and answer. We will be
keeping the word of God next Wednesday
by keeping the Passover in Leviticus the
23rd chapter. So there will not be a Q&A
next Wednesday, April 1st, but we will
resume our Q&A back on April the 8th.
So with that being said, sister Deborah,
what is our first question of the
evening?
Uh yes, there are several held over
questions that will be answered first
before getting into tonight's Q&A.
J- Jester asked, "In 1 Corinthians 2
verses 7 through 11, 11 being the crux,
some may go to verse 11 to claim that
the Holy Spirit is also God in regards
to the Trinity. What exactly does this
mean?"
All right, 1 Corinthians 2:7-11.
Brother Jerome.
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, the Holy Spirit um
definitely not God. Um
and oftentimes when they read that 1
John um chapter 5 verse 7,
it's not [clears throat] saying that
these three are God, okay? But anyway,
let's go read those verses that you gave
for the question.
Um 1 Corinthians chapter 2 verse 7
through 11.
All right.
Go ahead. [clears throat]
But the wisdom of God in a mystery, even
the hidden wisdom, which God ordained
before the world unto our glory,
which none of the princes of this world
knew.
For had they known it, they would not
have crucified the Lord of glory.
But as it is written, eye hath not seen,
nor ear heard, neither have entered into
the heart of man, the things which God
hath prepared for them that love him.
But God hath revealed them unto us by
his Spirit. For the Spirit searcheth all
things, yea, the deep things of God.
For what man knoweth the things of a
man, save the spirit of man which is in
him? Even so the things of God knoweth
no man,
but the Spirit of God.
Yeah, so
>> [clears throat]
>> in that verse 11,
it's not saying that the spirit in that
verse
is God, you know? Um
but if you read that verse 12, it'll let
you know the spirit he was actually
referring to is his word. So read that
verse 12.
Now we have received, not the spirit of
the world, but the spirit which is of
God,
that we might know the things that are
freely given to us of God. Yeah, he
he's given freely to us by his spirit,
you know, he he tells us through his
word, okay? So let's go to uh
um Saint John chapter 6 and read verse
63 and that'll be it.
Saint John 6:63.
It is the spirit that quickeneth,
the flesh
>> [snorts]
>> profiteth nothing.
The words that I speak unto you,
they are spirit, and they are life.
Uh that's all I got.
All right.
Thank you for that, brother, as we move
on to our next question.
Next one, Be Alert asked, "At which
feast does Jesus make his last
invitation for salvation?
Is it also the same feast Jesus offer
all who are accepted to the Father's
kingdom?"
All right, talking about the word
invitation for salvation. Brother
Julius.
Uh thank you for the question.
Uh throughout Jesus from the beginning
of of his ministry until the end of his
ministry, he offered salvation to uh all
people all people. He just used the Jews
to preach to all people. But let's go to
Saint John.
Let's go to Saint John the seventh
chapter.
And Jesus said something on the eighth
day,
the feast of the eighth day. Saint John
and we're going to read verse 37,
Tanzil.
Saint John 7 and 37.
When you get it, brother, go ahead and
read it.
In the last day, that great day of the
feast,
Jesus stood and cried, saying, "If any
man thirst, let him come unto me and
drink.
Go ahead.
He that believeth on me, as the
scripture hath said, out of his belly
shall flow rivers of living water."
This is right here is what he said
uh at the eighth day feast, okay? Which
is the eighth day. If any man thirst,
that's an invitation to all.
Let him come unto me and drink. He that
believeth on me, as the scripture hath
said,
out of his belly shall flow rivers of
living water. He's offering eternal life
to anybody that comes.
And that was the eighth day feast. But
in Isaiah 56th chapter, he told you my
house shall be called a house of prayer
for all people. Yes, that's the same
feast because you getting into Jesus'
kingdom, you're going into the Father's
kingdom.
So
um
that's all I got on that. And then March
the 16th, he told you uh preach the
gospel to every creature. Matthew
28, he told you teach all nations. So
throughout his ministry, he always
invited people to salvation.
That's all I got, Cornell.
All right. Thank God for that
invitation. All right, we hope that
answered your question as we move on to
our next.
Moving on, Israel Goddess asked, "So
with keeping the sabbath, are we allowed
to get Amazon deliveries that have
already been pre-ordered on the Sabbath
day.
Well, you know, as we know, the Sabbath
day is a holy day and we're supposed to
do the best we can to keep it.
Um, you can request your your order, you
know, early in the week, which gives you
a couple of days for it to come, which
doesn't have to fall on the Sabbath day.
And also, you can request a particular
day to have your package delivered, but
if the Sabbath is the only day that that
package can be delivered to you, then
um,
you just have to let it flow that way. I
mean, it's just like the regular mail
delivery that we get in our mailboxes.
When they deliver on Saturday, there's
nothing you can do about that, but do
the best you can and um,
beware of the porch pirates. They're
everywhere.
Ain't that right, brother Drake?
That's right.
That's right. All right. So, do the best
you can.
All right.
Hope that answered your question as we
move on to our next.
Next one, lovely Cole says, I've been
down lately. Life haven't been great.
Been sad and stuff. Any verse or prayer
that can help me out?
All right, brother Drake, look like some
sadness and downness is taking place
here.
Um, you got some word for him, brother?
Yeah, let's go to uh, Psalm 34.
And welcome to the club.
You know, in Ecclesiastes, it says with
much wisdom is much sorrow.
Mhm. And at the same time,
you're going to be rejected of many, but
let's look at Psalm 34 and pick it up at
verse 18. Brother Tenzel, go ahead when
you get it.
The Lord is nigh
unto them that are of a broken heart.
And save us as be of a contrite spirit.
Mhm. Many are the afflictions of the
righteous.
But the Lord delivereth him out of them
all.
And this is what you got to keep in mind
while you're going through
sorrow and afflictions,
you got to put your mind on the prize,
on the focus
at hand. Skip down to verse 22 and read
that.
The Lord redeemeth the souls of his
servants. And none of them that trust in
him
shall be desolate. That's right. So,
that's what you're looking for cuz this
life is short. And the problems that we
have are shorter, but while we're in
them,
they they seem like they don't end, but
keep your trust in the Lord. One two
more places. Let's go to uh, Revelation
21.
Revelation 21 and pick it up at verse
three.
Revelation 21 and three. Go ahead,
brother.
And I heard a great voice out of heaven
saying, "Behold, the tabernacle of God
is with men.
And he will dwell with them. And they
shall be his people, and God himself
shall be with them and be their God."
This is what we're looking at. That's
the prize that you want to keep your
eyes on. Go ahead.
And God shall wipe away all tears from
their eyes.
And there shall be no more death,
neither sorrow, nor crying, neither
shall there be any more pain. For the
former things are passed away. So, all
these things you're talking about you're
feeling now, that's going to be passed
away if you endure faithfully. Go ahead,
read the next verse.
And he that sat upon the throne said,
"Behold, I make all things new."
And he said unto me, "Write, for these
words are true and faithful." Hey, the
word of God is true and you can put your
faith in it. One last place,
Isaiah 25 8 and 9. That's it. Isaiah 25
8 and 9. When you get there, read that,
brother.
He will swallow up death in victory. And
the Lord God will wipe
away tears from off all faces.
And the rebuke of his people shall he
take away from from off all the earth.
For the Lord have spoken it. Go ahead.
It shall be said in that day, "Lo, this
is our God.
We have waited for him, and he will save
us.
This is the Lord. We have waited for
him.
We will be glad and rejoice in his
salvation." And if you keep your mind on
this and be faithful, you're going to be
all right.
But if you keep your mind on your
troubles, you're going to be tormented.
Right.
>> So, you got a choice. That's all I got.
All right. Thank you for that, brother.
Hope it answered their question as we
move on to our next one.
Next one, Victoria Smith asks, "Can you
provide some scriptures regarding
interracial marriages?
I told someone that we are not to marry
other nations, but their response was,
'You can't help who you fall in love
with.'"
All right. Scriptures regarding
interracial marriage and
not being able to help who you fall in
love with. Yes, caller.
Yes, I'm looking at this.
You know, we've dealt with this
uh,
person
many times.
I don't feel no reason to address it
again.
Especially when you have a statement
like you can't
uh, uh, help who you fall in love with.
That tell me that's a person that want
to do what they want to do anyway. Yes,
sir.
I don't care how many times we put the
scriptures up and show them the Lord
where the Lord say you should not
uh, uh, marry outside of your nation.
It's not going to do any good.
So, I'm not going to go through it
again, put scriptures up that people
don't listen to.
That's all I got to say.
All right. We'll leave it right there as
we move on to our next question.
Next one, Ninja Stringer asks for
understanding
from scripture,
Exodus 20:29,
offering of cattle, fruit, and firstborn
sons to God. God says the firstborn
of thy sons, you should give to me. And
in Exodus 34:10-20
says, "Redeem the firstborn."
All right. So, we're talking about uh,
cattle, fruit, firstborn. Brother
Jerome.
Let's go read the verses. Exodus 22:29.
Verse 29.
When you get it, go ahead and read.
And thou shall not delay to offer the
first of thy ripe fruit and of thy
liquor, the firstborn of thy sons shall
thou give unto me.
Okay.
Um, to answer that first half of that
question,
let's go to Proverbs
3:9.
>> [clears throat and cough]
>> Proverbs 3:9.
When you get it, go ahead.
Honor the Lord with thy substance,
and with the first fruit of all thy
increase.
Mhm. And this is what the Lord want us
to do. Um, and
you know, we pay our tithes and things
of that nature in order to accomplish
that. Um,
um,
now, that that second part of that uh,
Exodus 22
and 29,
uh, you have this Exodus 34
10 through 20.
But the last part of that uh, Exodus
22:29,
uh, you can read about it
in that Exodus 34:19
and 20. So, we're not going to read all
of those verses. Just read verse 19 and
20 in that Exodus 34.
All that openeth the matrix is mine. And
every firstling among thy cattle,
whether ox or sheep, that is male.
But the firstling of an ass thou shall
redeem with a lamb.
And if thou redeem him not,
then shall thou break his neck. And all
the firstborn of thy sons
thou shall redeem.
And none shall appear before me empty.
Okay, now,
to to better answer that, let's go to
that Exodus 13.
Cuz it's going to tell you the reason
why the Lord is saying this.
And then he's going to tell you about
the redeem part.
Okay?
So, go to Exodus 13,
read verse one and two, and then we're
going to skip.
And the Lord spake unto Moses, saying,
"Sanctify unto me all the firstborn.
Whatsoever openeth the womb
among the children of Israel, both of
man and of beast, it is mine."
Mhm. Lord said, "It is mine."
You know,
all that open up the matrix, which is
the womb. Okay? Skip down and read verse
12 through 15.
That thou shall set apart unto the Lord
all that openeth the matrix. And every
firstling that cometh of a beast which
thou hast, the male shall be the Lord's.
Mhm. Every firstling of thine ass thou
shall redeem with the lamb. And if thou
will not redeem it, then thou shall
break his neck.
And all the firstborn of man among thy
children shall thou redeem.
Yeah, cuz when the Lord brought Israel
out of Egypt and he told Pharaoh, "Hey,
if you don't let my firstborn go, I'mma
slay your firstborn." So, the Lord
redeemed uh Israel's firstborn, beast
and man, and he redeemed them with a
lamb, okay? And that's why the verse we
was saying in that in that 20th Read
that uh verse 20 again.
Stop at 14. In that Exodus
uh
13 13, I'm sorry. In that Exodus 13,
yeah, read that 15.
Okay.
And it came to pass when Pharaoh would
hardly let us go. Mhm. The Lord slew all
the firstborn in the land of Egypt,
>> Yeah. both the firstborn of man and the
firstborn of beasts. Yeah. Therefore,
sacrifice to the Lord all that openeth
the matrix, being males, but all the
firstborn of my children I redeem. Yeah,
and he said he would not only he
redeeming the firstborn of that of the
animal, the beast, he was redeeming the
firstborn of man with the lamb.
Okay. That That's all I got on
All right.
Hope that answered their question as we
continue to move on to our next one.
Next one, Valencia wants explanation on
1 Corinthians 15 verses 29 and 30.
1 Corinthians 15
29 and 30.
All right, let's go ahead and read that,
brother.
1 Corinthians 15:29
and 30. Okay.
Go ahead.
Else what shall they do which are
baptized for the dead? But if the dead
rise not at all, why are they then
baptized for the dead?
And why stand we we in jeopardy every
hour?
All right, so we know Jesus came and
died for the sins of the world and
because he rose,
then we know that the baptism is
necessary. But had he not risen, there
would be no need for no baptism, but we
know that he rose from the dead. Skip
up, brother, to verse 12.
Skip up to 12 and pick it up there.
Now, Christ be preached that he rose
from the dead,
how say some among you that there is no
resurrection of the dead? Because you
had the Sadducees going around anyway
saying that there was no resurrection of
the dead. They didn't believe in angels,
had their own program going on, but go
ahead.
But if there be no resurrection of the
dead, then is Christ not risen? That's
right.
And if Christ be not risen, then is our
preaching vain. And your faith is also
vain. Mhm.
But yeah,
and we are found false witnesses of God
because we have testified of God that he
raised up Christ, whom he raised
not up if so be that the dead rise not.
That's right. Everybody on this panel,
everybody got some wisdom, know that
Christ raised out of the grave after 3
days and 3 nights. Go ahead.
For if the dead rise not, then is not
Christ raised? Mhm. Christ be not
raised, your faith is vain. And ye are
yet in your sins.
Yep, and you are yet in your sins
because if Christ didn't didn't rise,
then hey, he couldn't have came and died
for the sins of the whole world. It
would have been a vanity move. Read that
next script.
Then they also which are fallen asleep
in Christ are perished. Yep, and all
those that died thousands of years ago
would have no hope because if Christ
didn't come out the grave, then neither
could they.
But let's go into uh Revelation 1 and
let's read two verses there. Revelation
1.
And when you get there, brother, I want
you to
to read that that verse 1.
Revelation 1, I'm sorry, and verse 5.
Go ahead.
And from Jesus Christ, who is the
faithful witness,
and the firstborn of the dead, Yes.
and the prince of the kings of the
earth,
unto him that loved us
and washed us from our sins in his own
blood. Yeah, so we see here that it was
Jesus Christ who was the firstborn of
the dead, who was flesh and raised to
God having back all power that he had
before he came into this world. And read
that verse um 18 for me.
I am he that liveth
and was dead, and behold,
I am alive forevermore.
Amen.
And have the keys of hell and of death.
Yep, so the Lord is telling us here that
it is he that liveth and he came and
died, but now he is alive sitting at the
right hand of the Father and therefore
we all have hope and we can win
salvation if we keep his commandments,
obey him, and be baptized in Jesus'
name.
That's all I got.
All right, we hope that that answered
your question and we're going to move on
to our next one.
Moving on, Marilyn wants someone to
explain about the 3 days of darkness.
All right, brother Julius, there was 3
days of darkness. Shed some light.
All right, let's go to Exodus the 10th
chapter
and read where it says exactly that.
I know the Catholic Church has a uh 3
days and three three nights of darkness
uh
unproven.
That's what they call the apocalypse and
all this kind of stuff before the
rapture. Let's deal with the book say.
And this happened in the days of Moses
when Israel is in Egypt.
Exodus 10, we're going to read 20 to 23,
Tenzel. When you get it, go ahead and
read. But the Lord hardened Pharaoh's
heart so that he would not let the
children of Israel go.
And the Lord said unto Moses, "Stretch
out thy hand toward heaven that there
may be darkness over the land of Egypt,
even darkness which may be felt." Even a
darkness that can be felt? Yeah. Go
ahead, brother. And Moses stretched
forth his hand toward heaven,
and there was a thick darkness in all
the land of Egypt 3 days.
3 days darkness. Go ahead.
They saw not one another, neither rose
any from his place
for 3 days, but all the children of
Israel had light in their dwellings.
Now, some people are going to Revelation
the 16th chapter and trying to hook that
up and make it 3 days.
You know, but we can't read that like
that in the scriptures.
That's all I got, Corneal.
All right.
Hope that answered your question as we
keep on keeping on.
All right, uh Yosuf asked, "Why did
Jesus curse the fig tree when in nature
it only produces in its ordained
season?"
Why did Jesus curse the fig tree?
Brother Trey, what you say? Let's go to
Mark 11 and pick it up at verse 12.
Mark 11 and verse 12. Go ahead and read
it when you get there, brother.
And on the morrow, when they were come
from Bethany, he was hungry.
And seeing a fig tree afar off having
leaves,
he came,
if happily he might find anything
thereon.
And when he came to it, [snorts] he
found nothing but leaves. For the time
of figs were not was not yet. So, this
fig tree didn't have no fruit on it. It
just had leaves. Read verse 14. Go
ahead. And Jesus answered and said unto
it, "No man eat fruit of thee hereafter
forever."
And his disciples heard it.
So then, afterwards, Jesus come into the
temple. Let's see what happened. Go
ahead.
And they come to Jerusalem when he was
went into the temple. He began to cast
out them that sold and bought in the
temple. And overthrew the tables of the
moneychangers and the seats and of them
that sold doves.
Mhm. And would not suffer that any man
should carry any vessels through the
temple.
And he taught saying unto them,
"Is it not written, my house shall be
called of all nations the house of
prayer, but ye have made it a den of
thieves?" So, they didn't make the house
of the Lord a den of thieves. So, they
ain't bringing forth fruit, neither.
Skip down to verse 20. Go ahead.
And in the morning as they passed by,
they saw the fig tree dried up from the
roots.
And Peter calling to remembrance said
unto him, "Master, behold, the fig tree
which thou cursest
is withered away."
And Jesus answered him and said unto
them,
"Have faith in God." So, Jesus say,
"Look, have faith in God." Now, let's go
look at this from another perspective.
Let's go to John the 15th chapter.
John 15.
And I want you to pick it up at verse
two, and we going to skip. John 15 and
two. And we going to skip.
Go ahead.
Every branch in me that beareth fruit,
he taketh away.
And every branch that beareth fruit, he
purgeth
he purgeth it that it may bring forth
more fruit. So, the Lord is purging
those that is in him that it they may
bring forth more fruit. Skip down to
verse five and read from five to seven.
Go ahead.
I am the vine,
ye are the branches.
He that abideth in me, and I in him, the
same bringeth forth much fruit.
For without me, ye can do nothing. Mhm.
If a man abide not in me,
he is cast forth as a branch that is
withered. And men gather them,
and cast them into the fire,
and they are burned. Just like that
tree that was good for no fruit, just
had leaves on it.
Now, read verse seven, brother.
If
you abide in me,
and my words abide in you,
ye shall ask what ye will, and it shall
be done unto you.
>> And if his if his word is abiding in
you, your will is to do his will. Right.
Verse 10 is the last verse. Read that,
brother. If you keep my commandments, ye
shall abide in my love.
Even as I have kept my father's
commandments and abide in his love.
So, that fruit tree was an example of
unfruitful Israel that got leaves, but
don't have no uh
no fruit on it. Right.
That's all I got.
All right.
Keep the commandments. Our next
question, hope that answers your
question, Sister Deborah.
Yes. Uh he also asked, "Where does it
say in the law a woman is to be silent?"
Where does it say in the law that a
woman is to be silent, Brother Jermaine?
Well,
it's something in Isaiah the 8th
chapter, verse 16 and 20 that I'd like
to quote to you, and then I'mma pass it
over with to the uh panel if they want
to add something to it.
But, go [clears throat] to that Isaiah
8.
And read verse 16, then skip to verse
20.
Isaiah 8?
Yeah.
Verse 16.
Bind up the testimony, seal the law
among my disciples. Mhm. Skip down verse
20.
To the law and to the testimony. If they
speak not according to this word, it is
because there is no light in them. Yeah,
so if you want the light of the word of
the Lord Jesus Christ, he wants you
getting his word out of the old
and the new, the law and the testimony,
okay?
Uh I'mma give it to the panel if they
want to add something.
No, I mentioned that 1 Timothy 2 about
being silent.
Okay. In the church.
That would be 1 Timothy 2 and and uh
1 Timothy 2 and 11.
Okay.
Let the woman learn in silence with all
subjection.
But, I suffer not a woman to teach, nor
to usurp authority over the man,
but to be in silence.
Yeah, so
that scripture lets us know no female
pastors. Be silent in the church.
Anybody else?
Well, you want me to toss 13 and 14 in
there just so they can understand why?
Go right ahead, bro.
For Adam was first formed, then Eve. And
Adam
was not deceived, but the woman being
deceived was in the transgression.
Mhm.
All right.
So, we hope that that answered your
question, and we going to move on to our
next one.
Next one, Linda Stringer says, "I
respectfully ask, if the Bible we are
reading today, the KJV,
is a result of the Roman Catholic canon
that they picked, how do we know which
books were left out that were written by
the prophets?"
All right. You got a little bit in that
question, Brother Julius. Go right
ahead. Yeah, the answer to this question
is really a reversal.
It is not the Roman canon uh that the
Bible is predicated off of.
Because the Bible was originally written
in Hebrew, Aramaic, and Greek, okay?
So, now, by the time the Roman Catholic
Church came along, the Bible was already
written. This is why they took it over.
They people was dying for their faith.
They couldn't beat it, so they joined it
and took it over and took it took took
it over and gave you Roman Christianity.
So, therefore, uh this book that we got
here,
uh well, let's let the book take We're
not going to do this talking. Let's go
uh
and show you uh 2
2 Timothy the 2nd chapter. We going to
start there, Tenzel. 2 Timothy 2.
And we going to read one verse.
And this is what you have to do, who's
asking or anybody that's asking this
question. Understand, either you believe
the Bible or you don't. The Bible is the
absolute word of God, and in it it is
salvation, and everything the majority
of it is backed by history.
Okay? It is backed by history.
Even uh uh go ahead. 2 Timothy uh 2. And
read verse 15. This is what you got to
do first. So, you got Let's look at what
the Let's look at what uh uh uh Paul is
saying carefully. Go ahead.
Study to show thyself approved unto God,
a workman that needeth not to be
ashamed,
rightly dividing the word of truth. So,
when you rightly divide the word of
truth,
the truth is the word of God. And when
you rightly divide it, either you going
to be believe it, you going to believe
how the earth was existed, how it came
into existence, what happens when you
die, why do you die? All the answers are
in here.
This didn't come out of uh Rome. It came
from Jerusalem.
The church in the wilderness, okay? Now,
let's go to uh 2 Peter.
And you could write down um
what uh Tenzel uh
Brother Cornell just said about
Isaiah
the 8th chapter, 16 and 20. If they
speak not according to that which is
written,
cuz this is the word of God. Otherwise,
it would not be holy. 2 Peter 1.
Tenzel, read verse 16 first.
2 Peter.
1 16. And then we going to skip.
For we have not followed cunningly
devised fables,
when we made known unto you the power
and coming of our Lord Jesus Christ,
but were eyewitnesses of his majesty.
See, this is why the Lord got this
written. The Catholic Church is giving
you cunningly devised fables, such as
the Apocrypha, such as the lost books,
such as all these other books. Go ahead
and read at verse 19 to 21.
We have also a more sure word of
prophecy. We have also a more sure word
of prophecy. You don't have to debate
anything with anybody.
But, if you will debate, let's debate
prophecy. Did these things happen that
are written in this book? Have they been
fulfilled? Will they be fulfilled? The
The Bible is a history book.
Past, present, future foretold. Finish
it.
Whereunto ye do well that ye take heed,
as unto a light that shineth in a dark
place, until the day dawn,
and the day star arise in your hearts.
That is the understanding of the word of
God in your mind. One more.
For knowing this first, that no prophecy
of the scripture scripture is of any
private interpretation. Cuz the Lord has
never hid anything from us. Because he's
the God of salvation, and he wants his
creation to have salvation. One more
place, and then one one place with one
verse. Isaiah 34.
Isaiah 34. Uh-huh. Cuz I hear this a
lot,
that Bible was written by man to control
man. Every book is written by man or
some woman,
but this book here is the same thing
designed to use salvation.
Isaiah 34, and just read verse 16.
Seek ye out of the book of the Lord and
read. Uh-huh. Not one of these shall
fail. None of it shall fail. Go ahead.
None shall want her mate. Uh-huh. My
mouth has commanded Yeah. spirit it has
gathered them. So, this book, the Bible,
all 66 books, 39 in the old, 27 in the
new, is the law and the testimony like
Isaiah said. If they speak not according
to this this word,
they have no knowledge in them. So, you
how do you do it? You got to read the
book. Then you see where the origin of
it from and then find out where them
other books come from. And they're not
in the Bible, they're not the word of
God.
So, that's all I got. Anybody else?
All right. Thank you for that there,
brother. As we continue to move on with
the time check.
Yes, the time is 8:11.
This comment might be funny, says,
This may be a loaded question, but which
scriptures do I need to read in order to
fully understand the 2300 days prophecy
in Daniel 8? I understand that 1260 of
those days are the great tribulation.
All right. So, guest caller is asking
about that 2300 and if you could shed
some light on that.
Yeah, well, the 2300 include the time of
animal sacrifice
and the great tribulation.
Let's go into Daniel 8 chapter and read
from 9 to 14.
Daniel 8
9 to 14. And out of
>> [clears throat]
>> And out of one of them came forth a
little horn,
which waxed exceeding great toward the
south and toward the east, and toward
the pleasant land.
And it waxed great,
Now, that little horn is the abomination
of desolation, which we call the pope,
okay?
Mhm.
And it waxed great,
even to the host of heaven.
And it cast down some of the host and of
the stars to the ground, and stepped
stamped upon them.
Yea, he magnified himself, even to the
prince of the host. And by him the daily
sacrifice was taken away,
and the place of his sanctuary was cast
down.
And a host was given
Now, let me let you know the sacrifice
that was going on, this guy stopped it.
Go ahead.
And a host was given him against the
daily sacrifice by reason of
transgression,
and it cast down the truth to the
ground,
and it practiced and prospered.
The verse 13.
Keep reading.
Then I heard one saint speaking, and
another saint said
to that certain saint which
Verse 12, Tinsdale.
I I read 12. Read again. Oh.
Yeah. I'm sorry. Yeah, go ahead, bro.
And a host was given him again the daily
sacrifice that sacrifice by reason of
transgression.
>> [snorts]
>> And it cast down the truth to the
ground, and it practiced and prospered.
Then I heard one saint speaking, and
another saint said unto that certain
saint which spake,
How long shall be the vision concerning
the daily sacrifice and the
transgression of desolation, to give
both the sanctuary and the host to be
trodden under foot?
Now, this mentioned Now, this this
mentioned both of them. How long you
going to give the sacrifice, the daily
sacrifice,
and the
uh
you know, the holy place to be trodden
under foot. That was the question that's
asked. Now, this is the answer to tell
you how long. Go ahead.
And he said unto me, Unto 2300
days, then shall the sanctuary be
cleansed.
Now, that is the
That is the answer right here.
There's going to be 2300 days. Then
shall the
That till the the sanctuary going to be
cleansed. So, what do we have here? We
have
We
1040 days of animal sacrifice.
Then we're going to have 1200
and
60 days of great tribulation.
And And when you add them together, you
got your 2300 days and the Lord said at
the end I ain't you said the end of
these days.
They're going to be terminated and it's
going to be cleansed.
So, now we got 1040 days
of 1040 days of animal sacrifice. Go to
Daniel 11 chapter
and read verse 31.
And arms shall stand on his part.
And they shall pollute the sanctuary of
strength,
and shall take away the daily sacrifice,
and they shall place the abomination
that maketh desolate.
Now, what they're going to do here the
army going to be they're going to have
this this U
European army over there, them 10
nations. They're going to be controlling
up to 31 armies. What they're going to
do here
the over there going to uh
build the temple
and they and they're going to start the
animal sacrifice.
Now,
European Union going to come to come
over there cuz I know that the
the ain't going to invite them
over there and they're going to stop the
animal sacrifice after it has gone on
for 1000
40 days and they are going to set up
the abomination of desolation,
which is
the pope and he is going to rule for 3
and 1/2 years. Daniel 12 and 7.
And I heard the man clothed in linen,
which was upon the waters of the river,
when he held up his right hand and
[snorts] his left hand unto heaven,
and swore by him that liveth forever
that it shall be for a time,
times,
and a half.
And when he shall have accomplished to
scatter the power of the holy people,
all these things shall be finished.
And so And that's how it's going to
be finished. It's going to start with
the animal sacrifice,
which is going to be 1040 days.
Then they're going to start with the
great tribulation, which 1260 days.
And at the end of that the Lord going to
come and he is going to terminate it.
Simple as that.
Second Corinthians
Second Thessalonians second chapter will
tell you that the Lord when this man
standing in the holy place
that the Lord going to come
and he is going to
terminate him at his coming.
But the 2300 days are not complicated.
It's just telling you that the
over there going to sacrifice for 1040
days
and the pope's people going to stop it.
Then they're going to set him up and now
he is going to rule for 1260 days, which
is 3 and 1/2 years.
And at the end of the 1260 days it's
going to be over with because the Jesus
going to terminate it.
So, that
includes the animal sacrifice and the
great tribulation.
That's all I have to say.
All right.
Hope that answered your question as we
move on to our next one.
Yes, so he also asked, Is the time of
Jacob's trouble just the first part of
the great tribulation that those with
understanding can possibly escape from
or does it start prior to that?
All right. What about this time of great
tribulation?
Guest caller.
Well, those things Jacob's trouble
started when he sinned against God.
Yeah.
Let's go to Jeremiah. Read Jeremiah 30
and 7.
Hey.
Jeremiah 30
and verse 7.
Alas!
for that day is great, so that none is
like it.
It is even the time of Jacob's trouble,
but he shall be saved out of it.
Okay? So, that one is none like it is
talking about the great tribulation. The
Lord said ain't going to be a day and
was never time before it and ain't going
to never be another time after it. Let's
start at Matthew 24.
We're going to read from 1 to 4 then
we're going to skip.
Read it when you get there.
And Jesus went out and departed from the
temple. And his disciples came to him
for to show him the building of the
temple.
And Jesus said unto them, See ye not all
these things? Verily I say unto you,
There shall not be left here one stone
upon another that shall not be thrown
down.
And as he
sat upon the Mount of Olives, the
disciples came unto him privately
saying, "Tell us, when shall these
things be? And what shall be the sign of
thy coming and of the end of the world?"
And Jesus answered and said unto them,
That's the world the end of the world
that we knew about it.
End of the world that men going to be
running.
And then what did he say? Go ahead.
And Jesus answered and said unto them,
"Take heed that no man deceive you.
For many shall come in my name saying,
'I am Christ.'
And shall deceive many.
Go ahead. Keep down to verse 15 and
continue.
And when you And when you therefore
shall see the abomination of desolation
spoken of by Daniel the prophet, stand
in the holy place.
Whoso readeth, let him understand.
Then let them which be in Judaea flee
into the mountains. Let him which be on
the house top not come down to take
anything out of his house.
Neither let him which is in the field
return back to take his clothes.
And woe unto them that are with child
and to them that give suck in those
days.
But pray ye that your flight be not in
the winter
neither on the Sabbath day.
For then shall be great tribulation,
such as was not since the beginning of
the world to this time, no, nor ever
shall be.
Now, that's what it let That's what you
know the Lord going is going to be
really rough. Keep reading.
And except those days should be
shortened, there shall no flesh be
saved.
But for the elect's sake, those days
shall be shortened.
Then if any man shall
No, this is it. Now,
when you when you see the abomination of
desolation, when you see the Pope move
into that temple that the going
to build build, let you see then you
better flee.
Now,
uh
and these are the people who have some
understanding.
These people are defined as not only
physical Israel, but these are people of
understanding. But when you you see the
abomination stand in the holy place,
flee. For there going to be a time of
trouble which has never been and ain't
going to be again. But now, let's go to
the Revelation the 12th chapter.
And
uh we going to read one and two and then
we going to skip.
And there appeared a great wonder in
heaven. A woman clothed with the sun
and the moon under her feet. And upon
her head a crown of 12 stars.
And she being with child cried,
travailing in birth, and pained to be
delivered.
Go ahead. And skip down to verse five
and go ahead.
And she brought forth a man child,
who was to rule all nations with a rod
of iron. And her child was caught up
unto God
and to his throne.
And the woman
fled in the wilderness,
where she had a place prepared of God
that they should feed her there a
thousand two hundred and three score
days.
Yep. So now,
this is the people that's going to
escape, but the majority of Israel
uh which is Jacob's seed is going to
don't know about this. Right. The people
that are going to go to the wilderness
place of safety, we know about it, but
the other
children of Jacob, they don't know about
it.
Right.
>> And they going to be in trouble.
Yeah. Where it said in in Daniel that I
didn't write it down where it said that
the when this man is operating, he shall
a lot of So those that knew do know
their God going to do exploit. But a lot
of them going to fall by the sword many
days.
Right. And some going to be killed by
others.
That's talking Jacob here.
Okay?
So yeah, great tribulation is the time
of Jacob's trouble. That's the I mean
real bad trouble. But like I said at
first, Jacob's trouble started when he
sinned against God. That's all I have to
say.
All right.
I hope that answered your question
there.
And we going to continue to move on.
Moving on. Uh Charlotte T asked, "Who
was the last apostle to die and what
Bible verse supports it?"
I don't know.
Open to the panel.
Me either.
All right.
And it looks like we all unanimous. We
don't know. So we going to
>> Cornelius, uh I I
on that question 11 about the Roman
Catholic canon, uh the person was
asking, "How do we know which books were
left out that were written by the
prophets?"
You got all the books that there you got
the 66 that are written.
Anything additional to that, you don't
need it.
Yeah.
>> need the book of Joshua cuz you can read
the book of
Joshua. So
uh I didn't properly finish answering
that question.
66 is enough. The law and the testimony.
Yeah. Old and New Testament get you
salvation.
That's right. Thank you, brother.
>> Old and New Testament. Yes, sir. All
right. And uh sister Deborah, as far as
that 14, who was the last apostle to die
and what Bible verse supports it, we
don't know.
And we going to leave it there and we
going to move on to our next question.
Yes, moving on to the next question.
Isaiah Richards asked, "In Genesis
2:1-5,
when was man created? Was it on the
sixth day or the seventh day?"
All right. When was this man created in
that Genesis 2:1-5,
brother Jerome?
He was created on the sixth day, not the
seventh.
The Lord rested on the seventh from all
his work which he had made and created.
So let's go read it. Genesis 1
and picking it up at verse 24, read it
to the 26.
And God said, "Let the earth bring forth
the living creatures after his kind,
cattle and creeping things and beasts of
beasts of the earth after his kind." And
it was so.
And God made the beasts of the earth
after his kind, the cattle after their
kind, and everything that creepeth upon
the earth after his kind. And God saw
that it was good.
And God said, "Let us make man in our
image, after our likeness. And let them
have dominion over the fish of the sea
and over the fowls of the air and over
the cattle and over all the earth and
over every creeping thing that creepeth
upon the earth." And skip down to verse
31.
So God saw everything that he had made.
And behold, it was very good. And the
evening and the morning were the sixth
day. So he had completed that which he
when he had made man,
>> [clears throat]
>> it was done in the sixth day.
Read verse chapter two and read read
verse one and two and that'll be it.
Thus the heaven and the earth were
finished and all the hosts of them. And
on the seventh day God ended his work
which he had made. And he rested on the
seventh day from all his work which he
had made.
That's That's all I got.
All right. Thank you for that, brother.
As we move on to our next question.
Next one, Cashin asked, "In Exodus 15:20
and also Judges 4:4,
are the two places that mention female
prophetesses?
They want to know, did we have female
prophets?"
All right. Did we have female prophets
in that Exodus 15:20 and Judges 4:4,
brother Julius? The answer is you
answered your own question.
You read Let's go to the scriptures.
Exodus 15.
The answer is yes.
Exodus 15, you it just named two of
them.
Right here. Exodus 15, let me read verse
20.
And Miriam the prophetess, the sister of
Aaron, took a timbrel in her hand and
all the women went out after her with
timbrels and with dances.
And how did it start again?
How did it start again, Tenzillo?
And Miriam the prophetess The
prophetess.
That's one.
Judges 4:4.
Judges 4 and read verse four.
And Deborah, a prophetess,
the wife of Lapidoth, Nebdoth, she
judged Israel at that time.
So you got Deborah. She was She was a
prophetess.
Go to uh Nehemiah 6
and read
14. Nehemiah 6:14.
Second Chronicles, Ezra, and then the
book of Nehemiah. Mhm.
Nehemiah 6 and 14. When you get it,
Tenzel, go ahead and read.
My God, think thou upon Tobiah and
Sanballat according to these their
works, and on the prophetess
Noadiah and the rest of the prophet
prophets that would have put me in fear.
Right. So, you got Noadiah,
a prophetess.
Uh uh
and then you go to 2 Kings on your own,
2 Kings 22:14,
you got Hulda.
Luke 2 and 36, you got Anna.
And then you got uh uh Acts the 21st
chapter, verses 8 and 9, Philip's four
daughters, they did prophesy.
So, uh
and and you got that wicked woman,
Jezebel,
Yeah. Uh in Kings.
So, she was a female false prophetess.
So, yes, Israel had uh prophets and they
had prophetesses.
The Jezebel was a high priestess, false
prophetess of Baal.
That's all I got.
And can I can I just add to that that
all those you named, Julius, none of
them were teaching in the church or nor
were they over any church. Exactly.
That's right. Yes, caller.
Yes, caller.
>> Yeah, but
but you said a prophetess,
but there was more to that. I thought I
had something else to this question,
too.
Oh, did we have
female
prophets?
>> Prophetesses.
Right. Well, we had
>> Did we have female prophets?
Yeah, we did. Yes, we did. Yeah, they
was there. Because anybody can bring a
message. Lord can send a message by
anybody. Yep.
>> I don't ever
We don't have none that nowadays, we
don't have any male prophets nowadays.
Teach.
>> So, the Lord
he done called the end from the
beginning.
The whole story is told.
Only thing left now is priests
and teachers.
Mhm.
>> And women can't be the one of them.
That's all I have to say.
All right. That was good add-on there,
and we hope that that answered their
question as we move on to our next
question with a time check.
Yes, the time is 8:33.
Angela Burns says, "Can you explain what
is meant when Noah's son saw his
nakedness?
Some say he saw Noah's wife naked. Some
say he slept with his own mother, and
that is why he cursed his grandson.
And some says he slept with Noah. What
caused him to curse his grandson? And
this uh scripture given is Genesis
9:22-25."
All right, we got some stuff in this
question that we know is incorrect, but
Brother Dre, would you
share some light on this question,
please?
Well, let's go to uh Leviticus 18, and
we going to see how they twist this
scripture
to say it said something in Genesis 9
that it did not say.
But, let's go to Leviticus 18, read
verses 6 through 8.
Go ahead and read it when you get it,
Tenzel.
None of you shall approach to any that
is near kin to him to uncover their
nakedness. I am the Lord. Mhm. Nakedness
of thy father or the nakedness of thy
mother shall thou not uncover. She is
thy mother, thou shall not uncover her
nakedness.
Mhm.
>> And the nakedness of thy father's wife
that shall thou not uncover, it is thy
father's nakedness. So, the nakedness of
thy father's wife shall thou not
uncover, it is thy father's nakedness.
So, they read this
and they say, "Well, that is talking
about Noah's wife." But, let's go over
to Genesis 9 now and look at it.
Let's see if this is Noah's
wife here.
Genesis 9, and we going to pick it up at
verse 20.
Genesis 9 and 20. Go ahead, brother.
And Noah began to be a husbandman, and
he planted a vineyard. And he drank of
the wine and was drunken, and he was
uncovered within his tent. So, Noah's
wife drunk of the wine and she was
drunken, and she was uncovered in his
tent.
No. No. It didn't say that, and it said,
"And he drank of the wine and was
drunken and was uncovered within his
tent." Verse 22. Go ahead. And Ham, the
father of Canaan, saw the nakedness of
his father, and told his two brothers
without. What do you see with?
You see with your eyes. Right.
>> It didn't say that that
uh
Ham
went into his father or went into his
mother. It says that Ham and Ham saw the
nakedness of his father and told his two
brethren without. What happened next? Go
ahead.
And Shem and Japheth took a garment and
laid it upon both their shoulders and
went backwards
and covered the nakedness of their
father.
And their faces were backwards, and they
saw not their father's nakedness. So,
they went backwards with a blanket and
covered their father's nakedness. Right.
So, all of them stories that they come
up with,
that it comes from a polluted mindset.
Don't have nothing to do with all that
other stuff. Right.
That's all I got.
All right. Thank you for You all get
guest caller?
Brother again, too, why would
the Lord curse Canaan's or Ham's the
fourth son? He wasn't even there.
Mhm. Exactly.
Don't make sense.
That's all I want to say.
All right.
We hope that that answered your question
as we continue to move on.
Moving on, Joanna Rosario asked, "Was
Jesus God here on Earth?"
Was Jesus God here on Earth? Brother
Julius, was he? No.
No.
He was not God here on Earth. He was
filled with the spirit of God without
measure, but he himself was not God on
Earth. Let me show you what he called
himself. Let's go to Luke the 9th
chapter, Tenzel.
And I mean, he said it
throughout his ministry. But, let's deal
with Luke the 9th chapter.
Luke 9, and we going to read verses 20
to 22. Luke 9:20-22.
When you get it, Tenzel, go ahead and
read. And he said unto them, "But whom
say ye that I am?" Uh-huh. Peter
answered and said,
"The Christ of God."
The Christ, the anointed one of God.
Not God, the anointed one of God. Go
ahead.
And he straightly charged them and
commanded them to tell no man that
thing. What did he say about himself?
What did he call himself?
The Son of man must suffer many things
and be rejected of the elders and chief
priests and scribes, and be slain, and
be raised the third day. So, now, he
said that about himself. He called
himself the Son of man. Because he came
as a man. When he came through Mary, he
came as a flesh and blood man. Right.
And he's telling you he said, "I'm going
to be rejected of the elders, the chief
priests and scribes, and be slain." You
can't kill God, but you can kill man.
So, no, he was not God. He was the Son
of God or the Son of man.
And he wasn't the Son of God until he
came up out of that grave with all
power. That's when he went back to being
the Son of God or God. Right.
That's all I got.
Let me throw in something.
Yes, sir.
>> In Matthew
in Matthew the 19th chapter, somebody go
read what this young man asked him,
"Good master, what should I do to get
eternal
>> Yes, sir.
>> [clears throat]
>> answered him.
Verse 17, Matthew 19.
Uh pick it up at that verse uh 16. Yep.
And behold,
one came and said unto him, "Good
master,
what good thing shall I do that I may
have eternal life?"
And he said unto him,
"Why callest thou me good?
There is none good but one, and that is
God.
But if thou will enter into life,
keep the commandments."
"Why callest thou me good?" Why would he
say that about that? Because he was
flesh and blood man. Right.
And he was not God. That's why he
>> No.
took to God.
Right.
>> have to say.
Yeah. He suffered terribly
as man.
Right.
All right. Hope that answered your
question. We're going to move on to our
next one.
Next one, Q and Lift ask, is it okay to
attend a wedding on the Sabbath day?
Sure it is. It's okay to attend a
wedding on the Sabbath day.
Sometime we have had a wedding ceremony
even within the uh sanctuary. So, yeah,
it's okay to attend a wedding on the
Sabbath day.
But if you go to the wedding on the
Sabbath day,
you are there for the wedding ceremony.
You're not there for the partying or for
the drinking or for the Soul Train line.
You are just there for the wedding
ceremony cuz it is still the Lord's
Sabbath and you have to keep it holy.
But when the Sabbath is over, then you
can join
in the festivities, but
not while it's the Sabbath day. Wedding
ceremony only.
And that's all I got.
And we hope that that answered your
question. Sister Deborah, can we walk in
new territory?
Yes, we can. Uh we are now into
tonight's Q&A for Wednesday, March the
25th, 2026.
Uh Shanquilla Akujo B ask, does IOG
offer any live podcast?
Um
any live podcast where callers can call
in with real life situations or
testimonies?
Uh he says these days on the social
platforms is more worldly knowledge over
God's word.
Okay. Um
Brother Julius, because you're part of a
platform, too, can you uh
address some of that question? Uh uh
yes, most of the times uh at the end of
a broadcast uh we have a podcast uh uh
uh Sound Doctrine Studio where they ask
that does anybody have any questions? Uh
Let Us Reason Together on Friday nights,
does anybody have any questions? And
then on the Balm of Gilead, every now
and then somebody ask a question, we'll
ask a question. But primarily
uh uh primarily uh Wednesday night
question and answer. We understand that
people are going through
uh uh things, but it has to be a
dedicated broadcast strictly for
answering questions. And um a lot um on
the uh Day of Atonement, on the Day of
Atonement, uh we ask a we have a panel
that answers questions uh live uh in
in-house and and and uh and online.
So, that's all I know.
Mhm.
All right. Anybody else? And
if not,
that's all the information we have for
you as we continue to move on to our
next one.
Yes. Uh Brett Brett ask, does cornbread
mixes, panko breadcrumbs,
and flour need to be thrown away for the
Passover? Is there a list I can find on
the IOG web of things that need to be
thrown away?
All right.
Let's open that up to the panel about
what should be thrown away
and what should not
even though it is a feast of unleavened
bread, which includes your cookies and
sweet bread and cakes and donuts, all of
that. That's part of it that has to go.
The bread that's in your house. No
storing it in the garage. No giving it
to your neighbor
uh
and anybody else.
The risen bread, the risen bread. Not
the ingredients, the risen bread.
Yeah, the cornmeal mix that's in the
bag, don't throw that out.
No.
Neither your flour. Yeah.
Have to be bread.
Yeah.
Baking soda can stay and other things of
that nature, so.
Correct.
And you can go to Exodus go to Exodus 13
and read verses 6 and 7.
Seven days thou shalt eat unleavened
bread. And in the seven days shall be a
feast to the Lord.
Unleavened bread shall be eaten seven
days. And there shall no leaven bread be
seen with thee. Neither shall there be
leaven seen with thee in all thy
quarters.
So, this is the feast of unleavened
bread.
Mhm.
>> Not the the feast of leavened
ingredients.
Yeah. Yeah, that's correct. Those two
Dre, we had a book that dealt with uh
the feast of the Lord, the do's and and
don'ts.
Yeah.
Okay. We have a lesson on the feast of
the Lord. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And we have lessons as well, so.
Um
wish you the best on your preparation.
All right, Sister Deborah, our next
question.
Yes. Uh Be Alert says, I heard various
IOG ministers say, the day of the Lord
is when Jesus returns. Is the Sabbath
day or is or is only a few months? How
long is the day of the Lord and when
does it begin?
All right, let's open that up to the
panel, the Day of the Lord. How long and
when does it start?
What is it? What is the Day of the Lord
also?
But if you read the things Joel 2 and 1,
start reading.
Joel 2.
And verse
>> Blow the trumpet in Zion.
And sound an alarm in my holy mountain.
Let all the inhabitants of the land be
tremble.
For the day of the Lord cometh. It is
nigh at hand.
Yeah. A day of
A day of darkness and of gloominess.
A day of clouds and of thick darkness.
As the morning spread upon the
mountains,
a great people and a strong.
There have not been ever the like.
Neither shall be any more after it.
Even to the years of many generations.
Now, that that includes Now, what you
read about now is talking about Russia
coming across the Euphrates. But the Day
of the Lord start when the uh uh uh
actually
start with the uh with the Great
Tribulation because Revelation tell you
that he is the one that going to bring
tribulation upon Earth.
Yep.
And then he is the one. That's why I
should blow you the trumpet. You know?
And he is the one that's going uh and
and uh
uh and when the sun and and moon go out,
then that's when he is going to be
directly involved.
But the Great Tribulation is also the
hand of the Lord because he said he is
the one that's going to bring tre you
know, uh tribulation upon man, the
trial.
So, uh
when that poop moving in that temple,
that's beginning of the Day of the Lord.
Cuz he's bringing it on.
Let's see uh can somebody find in
Revelation right quick where he said
where Jesus or the Lord said he is going
to uh uh bring tribulation on the world.
And he's going to put Jezebel through
her in it, too.
Oh, that's all right.
Two, I think.
We're in search mode for that. I think
you're right, brother.
2 and 20.
Mhm.
Yep. Yep. Uh somewhere around
is that the church of Thyatira?
Yeah. Yeah. That's Revelation
Yeah. Yeah, that'll be 18,
right, Dre? Yeah.
>> 2 and 18.
Go ahead, Tenzel.
And unto the angel of the church of
Thyatira, write. These things saith the
Son of God, who hath his eyes like unto
a flame of fire and his feet are like to
fine brass.
I know thy works and charity and service
and faith and thy patience and thy works
and the last to be more than the first.
But notwithstanding,
I have a few things against thee.
Because thou sufferest that woman
Jezebel, which called herself a
prophetess, to teach and to seduce my
servants to commit fornication and to
eat things sacrificed unto idols.
And I gave her space to repent of her
fornication and she repented not.
Behold, I will cast her into a bed and
them that commit adultery with her into
great tribulation except they repent of
their deeds.
And there's another area in Revelation 2
where he said
that the
tribulation which he going to bring up
on the world. Yeah, that's um chapter 3
verse Read verse 9 and 10.
Behold, I will make them of the
synagogue of Satan which say they are
Jews and are not but do lie.
Behold, I will make them to come and
worship before thy feet and to know that
I have loved thee.
Because thou has kept thy word of my
patience,
I also will keep thee from the hour of
temptation
which shall come upon all the world to
try them that dwell upon the earth. Mhm.
So, that hour of temptation is the great
tribulation.
Yeah. So, what the Lord start
when papa move because he is the one
that's
orchestrating this whole thing.
So, the Lord going to let you going to
let the world know that the so-called
holiest man
on the planet is going to be the biggest
murderer on the planet.
Right.
>> In the name of the Lord.
Mhm.
See.
All right.
Hope that answered your question as we
move on to our next one.
Next one, Joseph asked in Isaiah 8 verse
20, it says to the law and the
testimony. Did Isaiah have the testimony
of Jesus Christ back when it was written
and how?
Isaiah 8 and 20.
No, he didn't have it. He had the law.
Testimony started with the New
Testament.
All right.
He just wrote We did
We'll leave it there. We'll move on to
our next question.
Next one, Lion of Judah asked, will we
have about 45 days to escape to the
wilderness?
The temple is built and man of
desolation shows up there.
How many days to escape to the
wilderness?
Open to the panel.
>> The first thing here, the Lion of Judah,
I don't even know if I should even
answer his question.
You don't call yourself the Lion of
Judah.
Come on. You got a lot of nerve.
Jesus is the Lion of Judah.
Yes, sir.
So, go to 24th chapter of Matthew and
it'll tell you when you should flee.
Start at verse 24 and 15.
And when ye therefore shall see the
abomination of desolation spoken of by
Daniel the prophet stand in the holy
place.
Whoso readeth, let him understand.
Wait 45 days and run.
No, when you see the abomination that
makeeth desolation, then you flee.
Yeah. Immediately.
I'mma show you how urgent it is. Keep
reading.
Then let them which be in Judea flee
into the mountains.
Let him
which is on the house top not come down
to take anything out of his house.
Go ahead.
Neither let him which is in the field
return back
to take his clothes.
And woe to them that are with child and
them that give suck in those days.
But pray that your flight be not in the
winter neither on the Sabbath day.
But let me show you your urgency of it.
If you on the house top,
you don't go come off the house top
running. Don't even go in and pack
nothing. Exactly.
>> If you in the field, don't go back and
get your clothes. You flee to the
wilderness.
Yeah.
So, somebody said 45 days and then you
flee, that's not a statement that would
come out of the mouth of the Lion of
Judah.
That would have come out of the mouth of
somebody that's working with somebody
else. 45 days and you going to get
caught.
Mhm.
Because it going to be real
real close.
Go to Revelation 20 the 12th chapter and
start reading at verse
verse 6 when this woman fled. Let's show
you who going to try to catch her.
And the woman fled
into the wilderness.
You want 6?
>> Start at
Okay.
>> And the woman fled into the wilderness
where she have a place prepared of God
that they should feed her there 1,260
days.
Go ahead.
And there was war in heaven. Michael and
his angels fought against the dragon and
the dragon fought against his angels and
prevailed not. Neither was their place
found anymore in heaven.
And that great dragon was cast out to
the that old serpent called the devil
and Satan which deceived the whole
world. He was cast out into the earth
and his angels were cast out with him.
Now, that that has happened already but
I'mma keep reading. Let me see what his
attitude is about the woman. Go ahead.
And I heard a loud voice saying in
heaven,
now is come salvation and strength and
the kingdom of our God and the power of
his Christ for the accuser of our
brethren is cast down which accused them
before our God day and night.
And they overcame him by the blood of
the lamb and by the word of their
testimony
and they loved not their lives unto
death.
Therefore, rejoice ye heavens
and he that dwell in them.
Woe to the inhabitants of the earth and
of the sea for the devil is come down
unto you having great wrath because he
knoweth that he hath but a short time.
Mhm.
And when the dragon saw that he was cast
into the earth, he persecuted the woman
which brought forth the man child.
Go ahead.
>> And to the woman were given two wings of
a great eagle that she might fly into
the wilderness unto her place where she
is nourished for a time and times and
half a time from the face of the
serpent.
And the serpent
>> What's going to happen
when he can't get her? Go ahead.
And the serpent cast out of his mouth
water as a flood after the woman that he
might cause her to be carried away of
the flood.
And the earth helped the woman
and the earth opened her mouth and
swallowed up the flood which the dragon
cast out of his mouth.
And the dragon was wroth with the woman
and went to make war with the remnant of
her seed which keep the commandments of
God and have the testimony of Jesus
Christ.
Mhm. Do not. I'm letting you know you
have to get you have to run with great
urgency because if he can't get the
people that's running and got some
knowledge and get to the wilderness,
what he going to do? He going to turn on
her seed. These are the people that keep
the testimony of
the the commandments of God and the
testimony of Jesus.
Yeah. If you fool around with 40 45
days, you going to get caught.
Yeah, he chopped me.
That's right and you probably won't last
long calling yourself the Lion of Judah.
That's all I have to say.
All right.
We hope that that definitely shared some
light for you on that question. And
sister Deborah, time check in our next
question.
All right, the time is 8:58.
Uh I believe this will be the last
question. Valencia asked, can you
explain John 4 verses 35 through 38?
John 4
and verses 35
>> 35 to 38. through 38.
All right, let's open that up to the
panel. Let's begin at in that verse
35.
Pick it up at 34, Tenzil, and read on
down to 38 and then we'll open it up to
the panel. Go ahead, brother.
And Jesus said unto them, my meat is to
do the will of him that sent me and to
finish his work.
Mhm.
>> Mhm. Say
there are yet four months and then come
up harvest.
Behold, I say unto you, lift up your
eyes and look on the fields for they are
white already to harvest.
And he that reapeth receiveth wages and
gathereth fruit unto life eternal
that both he that soweth and he that
reapeth may rejoice together.
And herein is that saying true, one
soweth and another reapeth.
I sent you to reap that whereon you
bestowed no labor. Other men labored and
ye are entered into their labors.
All right, open to the panel.
Yes, calling.
All this saying that this is a joint
venture.
Some people go and sow the seed,
you know, and and and some watered, but
the Lord is the one to give the
increase. That's all I'm talking about.
>> Yeah, in that order. So,
I'd like to thank you for that
good last question of the evening for
us. Sister Deborah, time check.
It is 9:00 p.m.
It is 9:00 p.m. And we like to say that
we've ran out of time, and we like to
thank everybody from all around the
world who joined us this evening.
If you submitted a question to us and we
didn't get to it,
we will address that question in 2
weeks. There will be no Q&A on April the
1st, because we will be partaking in the
word of the Lord, keeping his Passover.
So,
no Q&A April 1st. We'll be back together
again on April the 8th.
And so, we want to say until we all come
together again, please be safe out
there, be blessed, stay prayed up, and
may the Lord have mercy on us all as
Brother Tyn Zael closes us out.
Our Father, which art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done in earth, as it is in
heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread,
and forgive us of our debts as we
forgive our debtors.
And lead us not into temptation, but
deliver us from evil. For thine is the
kingdom, and the power, and the glory
forever. In Jesus' name we pray. Amen.